ENVER TUNA SONMEZ

FLUTTER DEVELOPER

Ankara, Türkiye

Phone: +90 (535) 391 6506 E-mail: etsonmez01@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

I am Enver Tuna Sönmez. I am 23 years old. I'm interested in mobile application development. While in my role as GDSC leader, I was a speaker on flutter at multiple universities. I have been interested in flutter for about three years now. I like reading project codes to improve myself. I share the information and experiences I learned on Medium. I love researching and seeing what I learn by applying it.

EDUCATION

2020-2024

ZONGULDAK BULENT ECEVIT UNIVERSITY

Computer Engineering

COMMUNITIES

GDSC - ZBEU

GDSC Leadership

2022-2023

- Leadership
- Team management
- Project management
- Event Organization
- Finding Sponsorship
- Marketing

GDG - ZONGULDAK G

GDG Organizer

2022-2024

- Event Organization
- Network
- Marketing
- Teamwork

PROJECTS

RESTAURANT APP - GRADUATION PROJECT

- FLUTTER
- FIREBASE
- GETX
- MVVM
- GIT GITHUB

REFERENCES

• Kadriye Macit - Senior Flutter Developer

E-mail: kadriye@kadriyemacit.com Phone: +90 (541) 863 0719

EXPERIENCES

• KADRIYE MACIT YAZILIM LTD. STI

FLUTTER DEVELOPER - INTERN

July 2024-Aug 2024

- UI/UX DESIGN
- BLOC PATTERN
- MVVM
- GIT GITHUB
- LOCALIZATION
- UNIT TEST
- REST API
- FIREBASEENDPOINT
- FIGMA
- POSTMANGO-ROUTER
- CI/CD
- CI/CL
- GITHUB ACTIONS
- LOCAL DATABASE

FLUTTER DEVELOPER (FULL TIME) Aug 2024-now

• APPARELTE (APP STORE)



• LOGO TEKNOLOJI VE YATIRIM A.S Aug -Sep 2022 - GBM YAZILIM A.S.

FRONT-END DEVELOPMENT - INTERN

- HTML5
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT.JS
- FAKE JSON
- RESTFUL API

CERTIFICATES

- GDSC Leadership Certificate
- KOSGEB Traditional Entrepreneurship Certificate
- KOSGEB Advanced Entrepreneurship Certificate
- UDEMY Mobile Application Development with Flutter

- SKILLS

- Mobile Application Development with Flutter
- Front-End Web Development
- Leadership
- Entrepreneurship
- Project Management
- Team Work
- Public Speaking

LANGUAGES

• English - B2

GITHUB & SOCIAL MEDIA

- Linkedin: www.linkedin.com/in/envertunasonmez
- Github: https://github.com/envertunasonmez
- Medium: https://medium.com/@envertunasonmez